techcabal.com 2016-06-19

# Privacy Policy | TechCabal

This Privacy Policy explains what information Big Cabal Media Limited, (“BCM”), operators of techcabal.com gathers from you through its Site and how we may use it.

The only individualized information that BCM obtains about you through our website is information you voluntarily supply. We will use that information to fulfil the purpose for which it was supplied to us. In addition we may use the information to improve our products and services, and periodically send promotional email about products and offers which we think you may find useful.

BM may obtain non-individualized, generic information about your visit to our website through the use of cookies. Cookies are small pieces of data that are sent by a website to your web browser and are stored on your computer. Data derived from the cookies is aggregated and used by BCM for statistical tracking purposes and analytics. We use this information to understand general traffic patterns on our website and to gauge and improve the effectiveness of our website. The data is not used for individual identification BCM in no way relates your personal information to these traffic pattern statistics.

If you are concerned about the use of cookies, you may configure your web browser to either request your specific acceptance of a cookie or disable cookies entirely. You will still be able to fully navigate our website if you choose to refuse or disable cookies.

This Privacy Policy applies to this Website only. We do not exercise control over any sites that may visit from a link on our Website. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you.
